http://www.anxietycoach.com/privacy-policy.html

The Anxiety Coach
Menu
HOMEAbout Dr. CarbonellContact InfoAppointmentsWhat's NewMy Anxiety VideosPrivacy Policy
SELF HELPFirst StepsOvercome Panic AttacksBelly BreathingOvercome the Anxiety TrickExposure TherapyCoronavirus AnxietyWorry Too Much?My Self Help Books
ANXIETY DISORDERSOverviewAgoraphobiaGeneralized Anxiety Disorder (Lots of Worry)Nervous Sweating & HyperhidrosisObsessive Compulsive DisorderPanic DisorderSocial AnxietyTrichotillomania (Hairpulling)
PHOBIASOverviewBlood PhobiaFear of Vomiting (Emetophobia)Fear of DoctorsFear of DrivingFear of FlyingFear of Public SpeakingStage Fright
BookstorePanic Attacks WorkbookThe Worry TrickFear of Flying WorkbookOutsmart Your Anxious Brain
AnxietyCoach.com Privacy Policy
by Dave Carbonell, PhD
At anxietycoach.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use anxietycoach.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.Anxietycoach.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.
About Our Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that anxietycoach.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to anxietycoach.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.
Google Analytics Cookies
Anxietycoach.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available at https://policies.google.com/privacy.Anxietycoach.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on.
Refusing Cookies
You can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse anxietycoach.com's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Anxietycoach.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:To run and operate our site.To display content on the site correctly.To improve customer service.To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize your user experience.To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.To improve our site.To improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.Anxietycoach.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.Specifically, if you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will require your email address.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.If you purchase a book from us, PayPal, our payment processor will collect and store your name, email address, billing address and credit card number. Here is PayPal's privacy policy.This site lets you share content with your friends and followers on various social media platforms. Below are links to their privacy policies.FacebookTwitterPinterestTumblrRedditGoogle+Anxietycoach.com also uses Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.Anxietycoach.com offers RSS as a way to easily follow content updates. We provide links for easy access to My Yahoo! and Feedly. Before you choose to use either as your RSS reader, review its privacy policy.You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.Anxietycoach.com contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, once you have used them to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website.Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide while visiting such sites. These sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Always exercise caution by reviewing the privacy statement of the website in question before continuing to use it.
Non-personally Identifiable Information
We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.
Children's Privacy Protection
This website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.
Release of Information
If we sell anxietycoach.com, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.
Data Storage
Personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site  is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.Information is also stored by PayPal Inc. You can contact PayPal with privacy questions by using the link here.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to download and review that information, click on this link.You can also request to edit or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on this link.
Updates and Effective Date
Anxietycoach.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to anxietycoach.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.Last updated: June 28, 2018
Follow me on Twitter & Facebook!
© 2010-2020 David
Carbonell, PhD.  Anxiety Coach® is a registered mark.
P.O. Box 256539, Chicago, IL 60625312.912.9989
Last updated on November 18, 2020
